{
    "subject": "resource/Yedioth_Ahronoth",
    "predicate": "property/type",
    "object": "Daily newspaper",
    "human_readable": "Yedioth Ahronoth is a Daily newspaper.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9829633235931396,
            "question": "Is Yedioth Ahronoth a weekly or daily newspaper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8779409527778625,
            "question": "What type of publication is Yedioth Ahronoth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8540681600570679,
            "question": "How often is Yedioth Ahronoth published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7597873210906982,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges facing newspapers like Yedioth Ahronoth today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7221646904945374,
            "question": "Are there any other similar publications to Yedioth Ahronoth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6536197662353516,
            "question": "Who are the potential readers of Yedioth Ahronoth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6406087279319763,
            "question": "What is the primary purpose of a publication like Yedioth Ahronoth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6398448348045349,
            "question": "What topics might you find covered in Yedioth Ahronoth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4792436361312866,
            "question": "How might Yedioth Ahronoth influence public opinion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4581136405467987,
            "question": "What country is Yedioth Ahronoth likely from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Yedioth Ahronoth is a Daily newspaper.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1998_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might Yedioth Ahronoth influence public opinion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1998_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What topics might you find covered in Yedioth Ahronoth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1998_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary purpose of a publication like Yedioth Ahronoth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1998_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1998_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more queries!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document mentions that \"Yedioth Ahronoth daily, Israel's leading newspaper.\" and also describes itself as the \"nation's newspaper\". This suggests that Yedioth Ahronoth is indeed a daily newspaper."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided confirm that Yedioth Ahronoth is described as \"Israel's leading newspaper\" and mentions it as the \"Yedioth Ahronoth daily\", which supports the statement that it is a daily newspaper."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}